bestcarmag.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy | BestCarMag.com

## 1\. We collect

Our servers are designed to automatically record information about your activity on our website which also includes all the information sent by your browser time to time. This information includes various different things and facts such as your IP address, name of type of the browser you are using and also the webpage you were visiting before you came to our site http://bestcagmag.com 

It also includes the technical information about your Windows system and the language you are using.

## 2\. Cookies

Cookies are used to store your personal data while you are on our site and this also enhances the security.  
This doesn't take much of your time as only one pop-up launches every time you come to the Web site.

Some third party advertisements are also used to support our Web site http://bestcagmag.com financially.

Some advertisers may also use different technologies such as cookies and web beacons while they advertise on our project. This also sends these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense account) some information which includes your IP, ISP and the version and name of the browser you've installed, and in some cases, the version of flash you've installed. The purpose of this is to achieve geotargeting or to show specific ads such as showing sports ads to someone who frequently visits sports Websites accordingly.

## 3\. DoubleClick Cookies

Cookies can also be used for ad serving through Google DoubleClick which stores a cookie on your PC while you are browsing a website and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (this may also include some of the Google AdSense advertisements). Interest based targeting can also be enable through cookies which shows specific ads to you according to your preferences. Ads shown to you will be based on your previous browsing history so that only relevant ads are shown to you. (For example, if you have been visiting cooking sites, you may visit a cooking website while visiting a non-relevant site such as a sports website). It is to be made sure that it does NOT track your personal information such as your name, email address, physical address, IP address, telephone number, social security number, bank account number or credit card number etc. You also have the option to opt out of this ad-serving on all the sites using the link http://www.google.com/doubleclick/.

Here you can choose to disable or selectively turn on off your cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings. Also this is the page you should visit to set any preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  
In short, this affects how you interact with our site as well as the other sites. This may also include the inability to login to service programs, such as logging into forums and accounts. However, it is also to be remembered that deleting cookies will not allow you to permanently opt out of any advertising programs.

## 4\. Individual User Information

http://bestcagmag.com will collect personal information if you choose to become a bestcagmag.com member. We do not share neither e-mail addresses nor individually identifiable information with any third parties. The personal information we are to collect includes your full name, personal e-mail, cell, mobile and/or work phone number, work or home address, company or organization name.
